discmakers.com 2018-08-31

# Disc Makers Privacy Policy

## Protecting your privacy is important to Disc Makers.

Disc Makers ("Disc Makers") knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the Disc Makers managed domains (including, but not limited to www.discmakers.com) and websites or domain names, or any other linked pages, features, content, or application services offered from time to time by and related to or involving Disc Makers (collectively, the "Website"), submitting information, or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy").

## WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVER?

This Privacy Policy covers Disc Makers’ treatment of information that Disc Makers gathers when you are accessing Disc Makers’ Website as a consumer and when you use Disc Makers services as a customer (the "Information"). Also, this Privacy Policy covers Disc Makers’ treatment of your information that Disc Makers’ business partners share with Disc Makers. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Disc Makers does not own or control (such as third-party websites that you may access from the Website), or to individuals that Disc Makers does not employ or manage.

## WHAT INFORMATION DOES DISC MAKERS COLLECT?

The Information we gather from consumers and customers enables Disc Makers to personalize and improve our services and to allow our consumers and customers to set up accounts on the Website. In connection with the Website, we request and display some Information to other consumers and visitors of the Website, which allows consumers to identify goods on the Website. We collect the following types of information from our consumers and customers.

**Information You Provide to Us:**  
We receive and store any information you enter on our Website or provide to us in any other way. The types of Information collected include, without limitation, your full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, IP address, browser information, password, contact information, credit card or bank account information, transactional information based on your activities on the Website, and media consumed on the Website including, but not limited to, media viewed, downloaded, uploaded, and shared. In addition, note that all information you enter into your Disc Makers Member Account or Disc Makers Customer Account is information that you provide to us. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.

**Information Collected Automatically:**  
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Website or services. Disc Makers automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, geo-territory information, Disc Makers cookie information, the page you requested, and the media you have consumed (e.g., viewed, downloaded, uploaded, and shared).

Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our site and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. This type of data enables us to figure out how often consumers use parts of the Website or services so that we can make the Website appealing to as many consumers as possible, and improve those services. We sometimes share this data with third party services such as the Hotjar customer experience analytics service. The Hotjar service helps us analyze how visitors use our Website. We do not collect through the Hotjar service or transfer to Hotjar any personal identifiable information. We only use the Hotjar service to record, on a completely anonymous basis, information such as mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity as well as non-Personally Identifiable Information text you type in this website. Hotjar does not create a user profile for the purpose of tracking a user across unrelated web sites and will only use such information pursuant to its Privacy Policy (located at <https://www.hotjar.com/privacy>) Hotjar is an example of one such service utilized by the website. You can view a complete list of Disc Makers’ third party services at <https://support.discmakers.com/hc/en-us/articles/360001311067-What-3rd-party-marketing-information-services-does-Disc-Makers-use->

## What About Cookies?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. Disc Makers cookies do not collect Information, and except as necessary to investigate claims of fraud or other misconduct or as otherwise necessary to track purchases for purposes of calculating credit under our affiliate program, we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other personal Information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or email address is.

Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of our Website's most attractive features.

Ads and offers appearing on the Website may be delivered to consumers and customers by our advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Disc Makers and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers or other third parties with whom Disc Makers may work. Disc Makers does not access or control such third party cookies; please refer to those companies' privacy policies.

For more information about cookies, including deleting and controlling cookies, please visit [aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/).

**Right to Access, Rectify, Erase, Restrict, Transport, and Object to Processing of Your Information:**  
You may have certain rights regarding your Information that Disc Makers collects and processes. To exercise these rights, please submit a request to [privacy@discmakers.com](mailto:privacy@discmakers.com). Disc Makers may ask for additional information, as reasonable, to confirm your identity before taking any further actions. Note that some of our services and special features require certain Information and erasing, restricting, or objecting to processing of your Information may prevent Disc Makers from providing these services or special features to you. 

## HOW DOES DISC MAKERS USE MY INFORMATION?

The Information you provide is used for purposes such as responding to your requests for certain products and services, customizing the content you see, communicating with you about specials, sales offers, and new features, and responding to problems with our services.

Disc Makers may use all of the Information that we collect from our users to understand usage trends and consumer and customer preferences, to improve the way the Website works and looks, to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, and to create new features and functionalities.

Disc Makers may use geo-territory information to customize the content and services you see on the Website, as not all services are available in all territories or have additional restrictions that may apply to certain users of the Website.

Disc Makers may use automatically collected information and cookies information to: (a) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Website; (b) provide custom, personalized advertisements, content, and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; and (d) monitor aggregate usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed.

Disc Makers may use your email address or other personally identifiable information provided by you for promotional purposes or to communicate with you with information about a specific program or feature you have elected to participate in or receive information about.

## WILL DISC MAKERS SHARE ANY OF THE INFORMATION IT RECEIVES?

As a policy for all of our brands, websites, and services, information about our customers is an integral part of our business, and we may share such Information with our corporate parent or other affiliated entities. Except as expressly described below, we neither rent nor sell your Information to other people or nonaffiliated companies. We may share your Information when we have your permission, and we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our consumers or customers, collectively, use our site (e.g., we share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use their services and our Website, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal online experience).

**Third Party Service Providers:**  
We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples of such information include, without limitation, fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and email, analyzing data, processing credit card information, and providing customer service. Unless we tell you differently, such third party service providers do not have any right to use Information we share with them beyond what is reasonably necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Information for the above purposes.

**Business Transfers:**  
If Disc Makers, or all or any portion of its business or assets, are acquired, sold, or otherwise transferred, including in any merger or other transaction, or in the unlikely event that Disc Makers goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, consumer and customer Information would be one of the assets that is transferred to or acquired by the successor or acquirer (or a third party through bankruptcy). You acknowledge and agree that such transfers may occur in any of these circumstances, and that any acquirer or successor or other party acquiring all or any portion of Disc Makers’ business or assets may continue to use your Information as set forth in this policy.

**Protection of Disc Makers and Others:**  
We may release Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with any applicable laws, rules or regulations; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Disc Makers, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Opt-In for Promotions:**  
We do not share personally identifiable information with other third-party organizations for their marketing or promotional use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in.

**With Your Consent:**  
Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Information may be shared with third parties, and will have the option of preventing the sharing of this information.

## IS INFORMATION ABOUT ME SECURE?

Your Disc Makers account Information may be protected by a password for your privacy and security. If there is a password for your account, you need to protect unauthorized access to your account and Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. You are prohibited from sharing your exclusive Disc Makers login information and if you share your password or your Information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lost control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your Information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify Disc Makers and change your password.

Disc Makers attempts to protect user information to ensure that user account information is kept private; however, Disc Makers cannot guarantee or ensure the security of user account information. Not even the U.S. government appears capable of securing highly sensitive personal and national security information from unauthorized access, use, and exploitation. Unauthorized entry or use by third parties, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time, including your Information.

## WHAT INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS?

Disc Makers may allow you to access certain information about you through the account holder dashboard for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. As stated previously, any further request to access your Information that you have a right to access, you may submit a request to [privacy@discmakers.com](mailto:privacy@discmakers.com). Disc Makers may ask for additional information, as reasonable, to confirm your identity before taking any further actions

## WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE?

As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose Information to us; provided, however, that in order to purchase goods from us as a customer, to make goods available for sale as a client, or provide Disc Makers services to you as an account holder you will have to provide us with Information. If you are unwilling to provide Information, then you cannot purchase or sell goods or sign up for services through the Disc Makers managed domains.

You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the "What Information Can I Access" section above. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.

You may request deletion of your Disc Makers account by contacting Disc Makers’ customer support at [privacy@discmakers.com](mailto:privacy@discmakers.com). Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.

You will be able to opt-out of receiving e-mail notices or solicitations from Disc Makers or our affiliates by responding to a link included in each e-mail notice or solicitation.

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Disc Makers may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your Information and will always be available at https://www.discmakers.com/community/about/privacy.asp. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you via an e-mail notice to the e-mail address associated with your account. You and all consumers and customers are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when you or they use the Website after such changes have been first posted.

## THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS; LINKS TO OTHER SITES

The Website contains links to other sites from which you purchase or use products or services through the Website. Disc Makers is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites (including the digital service providers from which you purchase or use products or services through the Website). When linking to another site you should read the privacy policy stated on that site. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on the Website.

All Backstage deals, discounts, and giveaways are provided at the sole discretion of the advertising partner. Disc Makers, and its parent company, AVL Digital Group, is not responsible for fulfillment of any products, services, or advertised offers provided by the advertising partners. All customer service inquiries will be handled by the advertising partner. All Backstage offers are valid for a period of 7 days, and are advertised as such.

## CHILDREN

Consistent with the federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), we will never knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of thirteen (13) without requiring parental consent. Any person who provides their personal information to Disc Makers through the Website represents that they are 13 years of age or older.

**California Minors under 18 Years of Age:**  
California law provides additional rights to minors under the age of eighteen (18) residing in California. You may request the removal of any of your Information you submitted while under the age of 18. Note that Disc Makers can and would remove Information upon request from its internal systems but cannot guarantee removal of Information that you requested be provided to any systems outside of Disc Makers’ control. YOU AND YOUR PARENT OR GUARDIAN UNDERSTAND IT IS NEAR IMPOSSIBLE TO HAVE INFORMATION ENTIRELY REMOVED FROM THE INTERNET ONCE IT APPEARS.

## NOTE TO INTERNATIONAL USERS

The Website is hosted in the United States. If you are a customer or client accessing the Website from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, then please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and other regions.

**European Union and European Economic Area:**  
The Website is not intended for children accessing the Website from the European Union or the European Economic Area by children under the age of 16.

## BY PROVIDING YOUR PERSONAL DATA TO DISC MAKERS THROUGH THE WEBSITE, YOU CONSENT TO:

The use of your personal data for the uses identified above in accordance with the Privacy Policy; and the transfer of your personal data to or within the United States as indicated above.

_Last updated May 23, 2018._
